

PROFILE

9 years of web developing experience for multiple domains including business, healthcare, ecommerce, etc.

Blockchain developer with 4 years of experience for Dapps, NFT, Defi projects etc.

Excellent smart contract coding ability and skilled in developing blockchain projects using Hardhat, Remix, ether.js and web3.js.

LINK

website

CONTACT

Address:

1132 Granada Street, Fort Pierce, Florida, United States

PHONE:

(805) 214-8119

EMAIL:

phillipgrandi89@gmail.com

LANGUGAE

English

HOBBIES

Football Piano

PHILLIP GRANDINETTI

Blockchain Developer 4 years Full Stack Engineer 7 years Web Developer 9 years

EDUCATION

University of Virginia

August 2008 - May 2013

Bachelor's degree in Computer Science

WORK EXPERIENCE

Modea (Junior Web Developer)

May 2013 - October 2015

- Developed healthcare web application frontends using React.js, Redux and Vue.is.
- Implemented new user-facing features and built reusable components using React.js and Vue.js.

Kortek Solutions (Full Stack Developer)

October 2015 - July 2018

- Created flexible and scalable applications that help commerce companies improve their operations.
- Developed business projects using React.js, Vue.js and Node.js as business services.
- Built features in a full range of applications and services
- Optimized site code for speed and resiliency.

SoluLab (Blockchain Developer)

July 2018 - February 2020

- Developed clean, tested smart contracts with Solidity using Remix and Hardhat and deployed them on Ethereum networks.
- Built smart contracts for web 3 projects such as NFT, crypto wallet, Defi and etc.

Chainalysis Inc (Full Stack Developer)

February 2020 - July 2022

- Built Web3 projects based on Ethereum network using React.js, Redux, Vue.js, Web3.js and Ether.js according to requirements and development guidelines.
- Implemented robust, scalable, quick, efficient, well-designed software that is easy to maintain and test.
- Wrote clean, well-documented code.

SKILLS

